fans welcome to another installment of
粉丝们欢迎收看另一期
spring tips in today's installment we're
今天的分期付款的 Spring 小贴士
gonna look at JPA at the java
将在Java上查看JPA
persistence api now DP is a
持久性API现在DP是一个
long-standing API it's been around
长期存在的API
forever in a day and it has certainly
永远在一天内，它肯定
enjoyed a lot of use in the spring
在 Spring 非常有用
ecosystem and beyond and particularly
生态系统，尤其是生态系统
its most famous implementation hybrid 8
其最著名的实现混合8
has a long history with with spring I
与 Spring 我有悠久的历史
think one of the really really powerful
认为其中一种真的非常强大
sort of multiplicative things that
那种可乘的东西
allowed spring to to prosper or Yama's
让 Spring 繁荣昌盛
death embrace hibernate for example to
死亡拥抱冬眠例如
embrace or um's it did a really good job
拥抱还是嗯，这做得很好
of managing persistence right time and
在适当的时间管理持久性和
so hibernate is the thing we're going to
所以我们要休眠
use today although jpay itself is a
尽管jpay本身是一个
specification and it can be used with a
规格，它可以与
number of different implementations of
的不同实现数量
which hibernate is just one it happens
哪个休眠只是它发生的一种
to be the most popular and most
成为最受欢迎和最
pervasive one but it is just one there's
无处不在，但那只是其中之一
others for example like Eclipse link and
其他，例如Eclipse链接和
spring boot itself of course by virtue
spring boot 本身当然是凭借着
the fact that it's implementation it's
它是实施的事实
support is based on JPA doesn't really
支持不是基于JPA的
care which implementation you can use
关心您可以使用哪种实现
Eclipse link for example you could use
例如，您可以使用Eclipse链接
you know hibernate to view the number of
你知道冬眠的人数
different ones so today though if we're
不同的，所以今天，如果我们
gonna combine ourselves to just using
要结合起来，只是使用
hibernate we're going to build a new
休眠我们要建立一个新的
application as usual here at start at
像往常一样在这里开始应用
that spring that IO and we'll call this
那年 Spring 那个IO，我们称之为
JPA we're gonna use the my sequel
JPA我们将使用我的续集
support when use lumba to make short
使用lumba做短时的支持
work of some of the tediousness of java
Java工作的一些乏味
we use time leaf and the web support
我们使用时间片和网络支持
we'll come back to that in a bit we're
我们会回到一点，我们
gonna use JPA naturally and I think for
会自然使用JPA，我认为
now that will be enough that's enough to
现在就足够了
to get started we've got Lombok my
首先，我们有我的龙目岛
sequel timely web and JPA well hit
续集及时的网络和JPA深受好评
generate letter give us a new project
生成信件给我们一个新项目
which I'll open up in my ID IDE here you
我将在这里在我的ID IDE中打开
a o JK that zip and we're gonna start
那个拉链的JK，我们要开始了
with a very simple application we're
一个非常简单的应用程序
going to map two entities to a table to
将两个实体映射到一个表
a database rather and two tables in my
一个数据库而不是我的两个表
database and I've got a database running
数据库，并且我正在运行数据库
on my local machine I've got a my sequel
在我的本地机器上，我有一个续集
instance running on my local machine
在本地计算机上运行的实例
called CRM it's a schema there's no
称为CRM，这是一个架构，没有
tables there yet
那里的桌子
but we're gonna go ahead and use the API
但我们将继续使用API
to create those instances with Bailey's
用Bailey的创建这些实例
table so let's do that we have to tell
桌子，所以我们要做的就是告诉
Springs how to connect to the database
Spring 如何连接数据库
that's the first thing and this is not
这是第一件事，这不是
any different than you would do with any
任何与您将要做的不同
other JDBC based technology so my beta
其他基于JDBC的技术，所以我的beta
is Jo q JP a or just straight JDBC I
是Jo q JP a还是直接的JDBC I
covered JBC my Vedas and Jo Q and other
涵盖了JBC我的Vedas和Jo Q等
spring tips installments so this should
Spring 技巧分期付款，所以这应该
look at this point very familiar so I'm
看着这一点非常熟悉，所以我
gonna say spring that data source URL
要说 Spring 那个数据源URL
and it will be JDBC : my sequel : four
它将是JDBC：我的后继作品：四个
slash four slash hostname port which is
斜线四个斜杠主机名端口是
usually 3306 the name of the schema
通常是3306模式名称
which is CRM in this case and we're
在这种情况下是CRM，我们
gonna tell my sequel to not use SSL on
要告诉我的续集不要在
my local node we need to configure a
我的本地节点，我们需要配置一个
password I'll be CRM we need to
密码，我将成为CRM，我们需要
configure a username and of course
配置用户名，当然
that'll be username will be a serum as
这将是用户名将是血清
well now granted this should not live in
现在好吧，这不应该存在
a property file in a real application
实际应用程序中的属性文件
but um you know for now we're just use
但嗯，您现在知道我们只是在使用
it there okay so that's that's the the
那里好吧，那就是
basic bones of the configuration that we
我们配置的基本要素
need but we also want to tell JP a to
需要，但我们也想告诉JP a
generate the sequel for us so and say
为我们制作续集，然后说
yes it'll generate the DDL based the
是的，它将基于
schema tables and so on all the
模式表等等
constructs and primary keys etcetera
构造和主键等
automatically by looking at our our
通过查看我们的自动
objects now keep in mind you don't want
对象现在记住您不想要的
this property in production you should
此属性在生产中，您应该
definitely not get this property in
绝对不会获得此属性
production in fact I would normally put
生产，实际上我通常会把
this under a separate property file
在单独的属性文件下
called application - dev for example
称为应用程序-例如dev
where dev is the name of a spring
dev是 Spring 的名字
profile that you activate only on your
您仅在自己的个人资料上激活的个人资料
local dev machine so if you deploy into
本地开发机器，因此如果您部署到
production and you don't have you know
生产，你不知道
spring that profiles that active equals
Spring 的轮廓等于
dev then it won't get activated right or
开发人员，那么它将无法正确激活，否则
go a step further and use something like
更进一步，使用类似
flyweight or liquor base motivates our
轻量级或白酒基地激励我们
database migration tools which are
数据库迁移工具是
purpose-built for managing the evolution
专为管理演变而设计
of schema and rolling back if necessary
模式并在必要时回滚
all of it are
所有的都是
you could use in tandem with this but
您可以与此同时使用，但
certainly you wouldn't use this in lieu
当然，您不会用它代替
of that now we're gonna use generates
现在我们将使用生成
generate GDL we want that we also want
生成我们想要的GDL
to show the sequel that's gonna be
展示将会出现的续集
output here so GK is just a giant or and
在这里输出，所以GK只是一个巨人或
it's an object relational mapper and its
这是一个对象关系映射器及其
job is to take our Java objects or JVM
工作是采用我们的Java对象或JVM
objects and to map them to the
对象并将其映射到
appropriate constructs in our database
我们数据库中的适当构造
layer and when it does that it sometimes
层，什么时候做，有时
it sometimes does a poor job sometimes
有时候做得不好
we have to give it a nudge here a hint
我们必须在这里提示一下
there about what to do and we can't know
那里该怎么办，我们不知道
that it's doing a poor job and as we can
它做得很差，而且我们可以
see the sequel that is generating for
看到产生的续集
example so it's useful to have this
例子，有这个很有用
statement activated especially in
声明特别在
development again these two things might
再次发展，这两件事可能
be busy fallaway or development all
忙于崩溃或发展
right all right now we have our
好吧，现在我们有了
application and we're going to manage
应用程序，我们将进行管理
two types of Records one is called a
两种类型的记录之一称为
customer and a customer will be a thing
客户和客户将是一件事情
that will you know store the Davis it's
你会知道戴维斯是
a record that's going to manage customer
用来管理客户的记录
information so class customer and then
信息，然后分类客户，然后
customers will have a record of their
客户将拥有他们的记录
orders how many orders in they've made
订单已完成的订单数
right and then a signal that these are
对，然后发出信号，这些是
create entities like so and we'll give
创建这样的实体，我们将给
each one a primary key value and that's
每个一个主键值，那是
going to be turned into a and by the way
会变成一个顺便说一句
this is important notice that I'm being
重要提示，我正在
given the choice between using spring
给定使用Spring 之间的选择
datas ID annotation which is useful and
数据ID注释非常有用，并且
a number of different spring data
许多不同的Spring 数据
modules now although almost all of them
现在的模块，尽管几乎所有模块
in fact except for JPA so we'll use a
实际上，除了JPA，因此我们将使用
pays make sure to do the right thing
付钱确保做正确的事
there when it give both to auto and
当它同时给汽车和
granting unique
授予唯一
IDs right so these are not natural ideas
ID正确，所以这不是自然的想法
these are just automating our lamenting
这些只是自动化我们的哀叹
surrogate IDs and we can use that and
代理ID，我们可以使用它和
that's fine
没关系
and our customer will now have some
现在我们的客户会有一些
fields so I'm gonna say the first field
领域，所以我要说第一个领域
is called order first then the first
首先被称为订单，然后被称为第一
name rather is going to call the first
名字宁可叫第一个
no and I want to exert control over the
不，我想控制
column that's used to store this it's
用来存储它的列
caught this data okay so in Java code
可以捕获此数据，所以在Java代码中
it's gonna called first but in the
它会首先被调用，但是在
sequel schema that we called first name
我们称为名字的续集模式
by default it'll just be named after the
默认情况下，它只会以
field and if they had done something
领域，如果他们做了什么
like first name then it would have done
就像名字一样，那样就可以了
it would have underscored it they said
他们会强调
earlier would have done whatever we had
早先会做我们所拥有的
asked did you asked it to do be a
问你是否要求它做一个
strategy but in this case we're just
策略，但在这种情况下，我们只是
gonna override it on the on the site of
将在网站上覆盖它
the difference okay so there's the first
差异好，所以有第一个
and last names and then of course we
和姓氏，然后我们当然
want things collection of orders and I'm
想要收集订单的东西，我是
going to use a set because I don't
因为我不打算使用一套
really care in what order the data is
真正关心数据的顺序
returned just so long as I have a tomato
只要我有西红柿就回来了
oh you have set now this is a
哦，您现在设置了，这是一个
one-to-many collection I'm gonna have
我要拥有的一对多收藏
one customer and potentially many orders
一位客户，可能有很多订单
and those orders if you look at the
和那些订单，如果你看
schema are going to be key based on the
模式将基于
foreign key in the order table that
订单表中的外键表示
points to the current customer so we
指向当前客户，所以我们
want to join we want to tell the ORM to
想加入我们要告诉ORM
load the customer and then load all
加载客户，然后加载全部
their all the orders and a separate
他们所有的订单和一个单独的
query in one query though and load all
在一个查询中查询并全部加载
the orders by looking for the orders
通过查找订单来订购
that have the foreign key that has the
具有外键的
ID of this customer and sort of two in
该客户的ID，以及两个
order to in order to map that and say
为了映射和说
that this is a one-to-many relationship
这是一对多的关系
let's say that all operations should
假设所有操作都应该
cascade to the subordinate objects here
在此级联到下级对象
and then we're also gonna say that want
然后我们还要说想要
to remove the orphan records if there
删除孤立记录（如果有）
are any so we don't basically we don't
是的，所以我们基本上不
want to any extra orders laying around
想要周围的任何额外订单
if we should delete the customer right
如果我们应该删除客户权限
so that's that's there and then we also
所以就在那里，然后我们也
need to give it a clue as to what join
需要提供有关加入的线索
call them to use so when I say join
叫他们使用，所以当我说加入
column
柱
name equals and I'm gonna say it let's
名字等于，我要说，让我们
just say that we want the order table to
只是说我们要订购表
have a foreign key called customer FK
有一个称为客户FK的外键
okay now this is a another instance you
好吧，这是另一个实例
know this remember I'm imagining a
知道这一点，我想着
product order like an order on a website
产品订单，例如网站上的订单
and that's the that's an interesting
那就是那很有趣
table name because order is a reserved
表名，因为订单是保留的
keyword in certain dialects of and in
和中的某些方言中的关键字
certain sequence I like certain in my
我喜欢确定的顺序
sequel's dialect right and we don't want
续集的方言正确，我们不想要
to run afoul of the of the parser so I'm
违反解析器的，所以我
gonna rename this table to orders and
将该表重命名为orders，
you know just to be consistent I'll
你知道只是为了保持一致，我会
rename this one customers alright so
重命名这个客户好吧
there we are there's our two different
我们在那里，有两个不同
records they relate to each other this
记录他们彼此相关
is a one-to-many relationship you you
你是一对多的关系
know you could also do a bi-directional
知道你也可以双向
thing you could actually have order have
你本来可以订购的东西
a reference to the customer if you want
如果需要，可以参考给客户
in this case I don't really need it in
在这种情况下，我真的不需要它
this case but it's nice to have we also
这种情况，但很高兴我们也
want to have a excuse that's I think as
想找个借口，我认为
complicated as we're going to get with
复杂的，因为我们要去
this domain excuse mr. Park product code
此域先生。园区产品代码
and now our job is to write some data to
现在我们的工作是将一些数据写入
the database so we're gonna go ahead and
数据库，以便我们继续
use Springs basic JP support before we
在我们使用Springs基本JP支持之前
even get to spring data and some of the
甚至可以获取 spring data 和一些
more sophisticated support we're gonna
我们将提供更完善的支持
use the absolute basic support that's
使用绝对的基本支持
been in spring forever I mean just you
永远在 Spring ，我的意思是只有你
know since since JP came out basically
知道，自从JP基本问世以来
circa what is it now when did JP a
大约是什么时候JP a
camera as you know early 2000 okay so
你知道的相机早在2000年就可以了
that support let's see if JP a
支持，让我们看看JP a
applications writer we're just gonna
应用程序作者，我们只是
write some data to the database using a
使用以下命令将一些数据写入数据库
I'll call back to the stern here
我会在这里回船尾
application and runner and
申请和亚军
when the application starts up will will
应用程序启动时将
inject a current entitymanager so these
注入当前的实体经理，以便这些
importance in spring spring framework
Spring Framework 中的重要性
and so on for JPA originates I think if
以此类推，对于JPA，我认为
you had to pick one it's a new local
你必须选择一个新的本地人
entity manager factory team okay so
实体经理工厂团队好吧
here's the local Energy Manager factory
这是当地的能源经理工厂
bean and this thing it's been around
bean ，这东西已经存在
since Trudeau right right now if you're
因为Trudeau现在就开始
using spring form of five in mid 2018
在2018年中使用5的 Spring 形式
thing and you're going to be using the
的东西，你将要使用
Jaypee 2.1 support you have to have that
Jaypee 2.1支持您必须拥有
as a runtime image but um but basically
作为运行时映像，但嗯，但基本上
all this is a it's been around for a
所有这一切都是一个
long time and the the main thing that
时间长了，最主要的是
this does the main thing that this
这主要是
support does is it gives you a entity
支持会给您一个实体
manager that is aware of spring
知道 Spring 的经理
infrastructure things like transactions
基础设施之类的交易
and so on and it also gives you a entity
等等，它也给你一个实体
manager that is thread safe or rather
线程安全的经理
it's it's a proxy around a number of
这是围绕着许多
different entity managers that
不同的实体经理
themselves are thread-local so keep in
本身是线程局部的，因此请保留
mind the entity manager per the spec is
介意实体经理的规范是
not thread safe in this this is okay
不是线程安全的，这没关系
because the specification was written
因为规范是写的
for example for technologies like EJB 3
例如EJB 3之类的技术
where the entity manager would be
实体经理将在哪里
assumed to be injected you write
假设你写
something like this persistence context
像这样的持久性上下文
entity you manager okay and you can by
实体，您的经理可以，您可以通过
the way this will actually work in
实际的工作方式
spring I don't I don't happen to like
Spring ，我不是，我不是偶然喜欢
this style I tend to use constructor
这种风格我倾向于使用构造函数
injection so private final like that but
这样的私人决赛
the the the style assumes that the
该样式假定
containing object is going to ever only
包含对象只会永远
be used by one thread well keep in mind
请牢记一个线程使用
that spring objects are single tips
Spring 物体只是一个提示
there's one instance no matter how many
不管有多少个
threads so if you keep if you inject a
线程，所以如果您继续注入
pointer to a service for example that
指向服务的指针，例如
uses
用途
and entity manager and you make calls to
和实体经理，您可以致电
that service from different threads for
来自不同线程的服务
example the many different threads being
例如许多不同的线程
used to service requests arriving at for
用于服务到达的请求
example a servlet container well each
每个servlet容器示例
time you make a call to that service
您致电该服务的时间
you're invoking a method in that service
您正在该服务中调用方法
that then invokes the entity manager in
然后在中调用实体管理器
that thread in the or you know the
中的那个线程，或者你知道
original thread as a result you're
结果是您原来的线程
making concurrent calls than any manager
并发呼叫比任何经理
that you shouldn't be doing right
你不应该做对的事情
remember how EJ bees work EJ bees are
记住EJ蜜蜂的工作方式EJ蜜蜂是
pooled you have multiple objects in a
汇集您在一个对象中有多个对象
pool and the container the application
池和容器的应用
server gets an instance of that bean and
服务器获取该bean的实例，
lots an instance of that bean for each
每个都有一个该bean的实例
incoming request and then it destroys
传入请求，然后销毁
that bean or puts it back into the pool
那个beans或放回池中
and there's this whole passivation an
这整个钝化
activation lifecycle that you have to be
您必须处于的激活生命周期
aware of and so on so you go you know in
知道等等，这样你就知道了
new jeebies they go out otherway to make
他们外出制造新的宝石
sure that you can write code that is
确保您可以编写的代码是
essentially single threaded even though
本质上是单线程的，即使
it has to be used in a multi-threaded
它必须在多线程中使用
world well in spring it's just one bean
Spring 的世界很好，只有一颗 bean
you just have one object it's
你只有一个对象
multi-threaded it has to be
多线程它必须是
multi-threaded whatever you do in there
多线程，无论您在其中做什么
is multi-threaded and so if you use an
是多线程的，因此如果您使用
entity manager you have to be aware of
您必须注意的实体经理
that until spring actually creates a
直到 Spring 实际上创造了一个
proxy we give you a proxy of the entity
代理，我们为您提供实体的代理
manager that itself then manages a whole
然后自己管理一个整体的经理
pool of entity managers and make sure
实体管理者库并确保
that there's an entity manager on the
在那边有一个实体经理
current thread on what you're making
您正在制作的当前线程
their request so the result ultimately
他们的要求，最终结果
is that well it just works you can write
很好吗，它可以写
code that looks exactly what you might
看起来完全一样的代码
have seen in eg b3 circa 2005 but it
在2005年的b3中见过，但是
works right the benefit is that you can
正确运作的好处是您可以
just write code and move on so now we
只是编写代码并继续前进，所以现在我们
have this basic entity manager now we
现在有这个基本的实体经理
need to use infection we need actually
需要使用我们实际上需要的感染
run this code in a transaction right in
直接在交易中运行此代码
order for this to work so to use a
为了使其正常工作，请使用
regular naked entity manager you need a
常规的裸体实体经理，您需要
transaction so I'm gonna use I could if
交易，所以我要用
I were building a service I could use
我正在建立可以使用的服务
the add transaction transactional
事务性添加交易
annotation on the service and then all
服务上的注释，然后全部
the methods there and would be closed in
那里的方法，将在
a transaction whenever you invoke those
每当您调用那些交易时
methods but in order to be able to run
方法，但为了能够运行
multiple things on the same run method
同一运行方法上有多个事物
I'm gonna demarcate my transaction
我要划定交易范围
boundaries manually here using the
此处使用
transaction template ok the transaction
交易模板确定交易
template has already been wired up for
模板已经连接好了
us it's been configured for us
我们已经为我们配置了
by spring boot and it's been given a
在 spring boot 上，它被赋予了
pointer to the JPA transaction manager
指向JPA事务管理器的指针
ok JP a transaction manager there we are
好的，JP，有交易经理
and this thing is aware of GPA
这件事知道GPA
transaction so again that's a
交易，所以这又是一个
implementation of the resource local
资源本地实施
transaction management facility in JP
JP中的交易管理工具
and this transaction template gives us a
该交易模板为我们提供了
unified API that we can use to to start
我们可以用来启动的统一API
and stop the transactions to work with
并停止要使用的交易
them and so on so you just basically use
他们等等，所以你基本上只使用
the traffic template method called
流量模板方法称为
execute and everything inside that gets
执行，里面的一切都会得到
execute instead of transaction now one
现在执行而不是交易
thing I should say is that you could
我应该说的是，你可以
also use with JP a you could use JTA the
也可以和JP一起使用，您可以使用JTA
Java transaction ativ the API that is
Java事务是API
the client side middleware for the X
X的客户端中间件
open protocol and I've done another
开放协议，我做了另一个
spring tips installment on JTA and I
我和JTA的 spring 技巧 分期付款
encourage you to check that out and if
鼓励您检查一下，如果
you use JTA
您使用JTA
with hibernate and with JP a and with
与休眠和与JP a和
spring well suffice it to say there's a
Spring 足以说有一个
whole galaxy of things that you need to
您需要的整个星系
get right and in order to do that right
正确并为了做到这一点
but spring boot spring boot under the
但是spring boot下的spring boot
head goes out of its way to make that
尽力做到这一点
kind of thing work for you so if you
这样的事情对你有用，所以如果你
look at the JPA auto configuration here
在这里查看JPA自动配置
hibernate JP a auto configuration you
休眠JP一个自动配置你
can see that this is going to use the
可以看到这将使用
local container entity manager factor
本地容器实体管理者因素
beam and it's going to import the
梁，它将导入
hibernate JP a configuration and you can
休眠JP的配置，您可以
see that this configuration is code that
看到这个配置是
you don't want to write trust me you do
你不想写信我
not want to write this code this code is
不想写这段代码，这段代码是
code that configures hibernate and it
配置休眠的代码及其
configures the the JP so that it
配置JP，以便它
configures a JTA transaction manager
配置一个JTA事务管理器
based on either the application server
基于任一应用程序服务器
environments
环境
JDI bound transaction manager and/or
JDI绑定的事务管理器和/或
user transaction and it then configures
用户交易，然后进行配置
the properties that hibernate needs to
休眠所需的属性
know about the vendor specific
了解特定于供应商的信息
properties that hibernate needs to know
休眠需要知道的属性
about
关于
- then delegate to the spring JK
-然后代表 Spring JK
transaction manager except of course in
交易经理，当然不在
websphere where of course things break
Websphere当然会发生问题
horribly because Webster's weirder they
可怕的是因为韦伯斯特的怪异他们
know all the other app servers so we you
知道所有其他应用服务器，所以我们
know this code knows about all those
知道这段代码知道所有这些
atrocities and it it makes it work for
暴行，它使它适用于
you so basically you can get you can use
你基本上可以得到你可以使用
this it'll do the right thing for you
这会为你做正确的事
and if using and and if you want to use
以及是否使用和如果要使用
JTA as described in that other video
如其他视频中所述的JTA
you'll you'll you know it'll work
你会你会知道它将起作用
it just works right that's um that's
它就是正确的，嗯，那是
code you don't write that trust me
你不写的代码相信我
nobody else wants to write but it's done
没有其他人想写，但是写完了
for you right now we have this let's
现在为您准备的
just write to date it's very very very
只是写到目前为止，这是非常非常非常
simple data to the Davis using the
使用
making into the manager API so what I'm
进入经理API，所以我
going to say I'm going to say TT dot
要说我要说TT点
execute right that's actually template
执行权实际上是模板
and that'll give me an a callback and I
这会给我一个回调，我
callback has an expectation that I
回调期望我
return the value in this case I can
在这种情况下，我可以返回值
return null I could actually use the new
返回null我实际上可以使用新
transaction callback without without
事务回调，无无
result or something like that if I like
结果或类似的东西，如果我喜欢
but here I'm going to just use the the
但在这里我将只使用
version that takes a return value
需要返回值的版本
because I'd rather use a lambda form
因为我宁愿使用lambda形式
instead of having to use the anonymous
而不是必须使用匿名
inner class form that the the other
内部类的形式
variance request now let's read some
现在请阅读差异请求
data today the hard code some users you
数据今天的硬编码一些用户你
know I do this a lot so Dave I'd them
知道我经常这样做，所以戴夫我要他们
sire we write some people as customers
抱歉，我们写一些人作为客户
so Phil - Phil common web and of course
菲尔-菲尔公共网络，当然
mark comma Fisher so there we are we've
标记逗号费舍尔，所以我们到了
got some names I'm gonna split the names
有一些名字我要分开名字
into it's an array of names there and
里面有一个名字数组
then I'm gonna map each name
然后我要映射每个名字
into a tuple I'm going to split the name
成一个元组，我要分割名称
right into two into common into the
分为两成
first and last name and then finally
名和姓，然后最后
I'll visit the tuple of it visit each
我将拜访它的元组
tuple and I'm gonna persist the data I'm
元组，我要保留我的数据
gonna say this DM that persist new
要说这个DM持续新的
customer and here I've got the customer
客户，这里我有客户
now this customer needs a constructor
现在这个客户需要一个构造函数
and for JP a I want probably I probably
对于JP，我可能想
want to get errs and setters and equals
想要得到错误和二传手
and hashcode and all that kind of stuff
和哈希码以及所有类似的东西
so here I use I make heavy use of Lombok
所以我在这里我大量使用龙目岛
so I'll say at data at all our
所以我要说说我们所有的数据
constructors at no log instructors right
没有日志指导员的构造函数
and remember you need an order and
并记住您需要一个订单，
constructor for JP it doesn't have to be
JP的构造函数
public but you do need alright so this
公开，但您确实需要，所以这
is useful you can actually next to say
您实际上可以接下来说的有用
force equals true and you can do all
力等于真，你可以做所有
sorts of you can say access equals a
您可能会说访问等于
private and then force it was true so
私人然后强迫它是真的，所以
you could you could do stuff like that
你可以做那样的事情
but I don't care you know fine whatever
但我不在乎你知道
okay good so we got that now and we're
好吧，所以我们现在知道了，
gonna save some data now that we've got
现在我们要保存一些数据
our constructors the constructor that we
我们的构造函数
get is a it takes an ID for the null for
get是一个，它需要一个ID为null
the ID the first name will be of course
ID当然是名字
the first part of the tuple the second
元组的第一部分
name will be the second part of the
名称将是第二部分
tuple and then we'll just return a give
元组，然后我们将只返回给定
it a list of rather a set of orders an
它是一系列订单的清单
empty set of orders so there we have our
空订单集，所以我们有
data that was persistent into the
持续存在于
Gateway and now we're gonna use the
网关，现在我们将使用
entity manager to create a query so I'm
实体经理来创建查询，所以我
gonna create a query here select C from
要在此处创建查询，请从中选择C
customer see where what that's it
客户知道那是什么
actually we'll just do that and let me
其实我们就那样做，让我
say that one a type list of customer
说一个客户类型列表
data back what I mean by that is that
数据返回我的意思是
the query method will give us a head
查询方法将带给我们一个头
query object so here we are customer
查询对象，所以我们是客户
and with that I'm gonna ask for the
并因此我要
result this visit each one that comes
结果这次拜访每一个来
back
背部
so here's each customer and I want to
所以这是每个客户，我想
log out I'm gonna have Lombok synthesize
注销我要合成龙目岛
a log4j logger for me as well that's a
对我来说，一个log4j记录器也是
log info typed query results will be and
日志信息类型的查询结果将为和
then here I'm going to use Commons land
然后在这里我将使用下议院土地
to log out the information that we get
注销我们获得的信息
we got feedback because I'm going to do
我们收到了反馈，因为我要做
that fair bit for the time that we are
在我们当时的那段时间
spending together looking at different
一起度过不同的时光
results somebody just say Commons line
结果有人只是说下议院线
three
三
I'll bring that in it's the versions
我会把它放在版本中
already managed for me so I just have to
已经为我做好了，所以我只需要
declare it and uh and in the music so
宣布它，然后在音乐中如此
I'm gonna say log dot info to string
我要说日志点信息到字符串
builder dot reflection to string
生成器点反射到字符串
customers all right
客户没事
so there we are we've already got mugged
所以我们就已经被抢劫了
at in for don'twe so we don't need that
因为我们不这样做，所以我们不需要
goodbye alright let's see what we get if
再见，好吧，让我们看看如果得到
we run this code as written
我们按编写的方式运行此代码
our my server I think you're confused
我们的服务器我认为你很困惑
too my friend
我的朋友也是
yeah it was done in confused alright so
是的，这是在混乱中完成的，所以
we have some sort of error what is the
我们有某种错误是什么
error Oh zero indexed
错误哦零索引
very good so look at that we've written
很好，看一下我们写的
the data
数据
they've written the data we can see that
他们已经写了数据，我们可以看到
hibernate was a nice enough to to create
休眠足以创建
those tables for us in the last run but
上次运行时为我们提供的表格
we have to add the constraint here so
我们必须在这里添加约束
it's still doing some stuff and here's
它仍然在做一些事情，这是
the insert calls into three different
插入调用分为三个不同的
inserts and then the query that we just
插入，然后插入我们刚才的查询
that we just ran and since none of them
我们只是跑了，因为没有一个
had any other records we didn't you know
还有其他我们不知道的记录
we didn't visit any of those records we
我们没有访问任何这些记录，
got the we got everything as we expected
得到了我们所期望的一切
so there's the results the first thing
所以首先要有结果
in the last name in the empty orders
空订单中的姓氏
collection all right so that worked out
收集好，这样算出来
just fine next time what I just fine
下次我还好
let's go ahead and now add some orders
让我们继续，现在添加一些订单
to to see what we have right to see what
看看我们有权看到什么
we can do with that that nested or that
我们可以使用嵌套或
subordinate collection but in order to
从属集合，但为了
make working with JP just a little bit
与JP一起工作
easier instead of using the regular
比使用常规更容易
entity manager which you know to be fair
您知道是公平的实体经理
wasn't so bad we just rejected it and
还不错，我们只是拒绝了
used it life is good in order to make it
用它来使生活变得美好
a little bit easier I like to use spring
我喜欢用Spring ，容易一些
data repositories okay so I'm gonna
数据存储库好吧，我要
create a customer repository that's
创建一个客户存储库
going to extend the JPA repository and
将扩展JPA存储库，并
manipulate entity entities of type of
操作类型为的实体
customer whose hierarchy isn't type of
等级不是类型的客户
long now it would be I think it's
很久以前，我认为这是
probably interesting for the audience to
对观众来说可能很有趣
know that the JPA repository was the
知道JPA信息库是
first repository type supported in
支持的第一个存储库类型
spring data and it came from a
spring data ，它来自
third-party product a community project
第三方产品社区项目
maintained by what who is now spring
由现在的 Spring 所维护
data lead all over again okay called
数据再次重新引导好吗
Hades hade s and it had a you know it
Hades hade s，它有一个你知道的东西
has it had this interface based
有这个基于
mechanism for current data all right so
当前数据的机制还可以
that's the Jaypee repository and i can
那是Jaypee资料库，我可以
use this to read and write and save and
用它来读写，保存以及
manipulate data so we're gonna do that
操作数据，以便我们做
here let's create another transaction
在这里，我们创建另一个交易
okay I
好的我
you know I don't care what the status
你知道我不在乎状态
actually and in the status in the ten
实际上并处于十大地位
vector another we're gonna write data to
矢量我们要写数据到
the database we write orders to each for
我们向每个数据库写入订单的数据库
each customer so I'm gonna say let's
每个客户，所以我要说
inject a customer positive right here
在这里注入正面的客户
okay credit the final customer posit or
好吧，归功于最终客户
II and that's the constructor very good
II，那是构造函数，很好
and now I'm gonna writes our data to the
现在我要把我们的数据写到
database in there say we turn in old for
那里的数据库说我们上交了旧的
our status and get all the records so
我们的状态并获取所有记录，以便
it's a customer positive find all get
积极寻找所有客户
all the customers back and then from
所有的顾客，然后从
each customer I want to create some more
我想创建更多的每个客户
data so I'm going to put some orders I'm
数据，所以我要下订单
gonna say int max equals math dot random
要说int max等于数学点随机
times five and we want to turn that into
乘以五，我们想把它变成
an integer and then test it right so
一个整数，然后正确测试
there's our count count of orders and
这是我们的订单计数
we're gonna say for int I equals zero I
我们要说int我等于零我
is less than count of orders I plus plus
小于我加加的订单数
and we'll add a record for the customers
我们将为客户添加一条记录
orders collection giving it a consistent
订单收集使其保持一致
view right so what we're gonna be able
正确查看，以便我们能够
to query that later so skew will be skew
稍后查询，以便偏斜
and missus that I - it's not real you
和小姐，我-这不是真实的你
look like but it's fine
看起来像但是很好
very good and so now we've got a number
非常好，所以现在我们有一些
of different records each of which is
不同的记录，每个记录是
gonna have their own Real ID but they
会有自己的真实身份证，但他们
should have
应该有
okay there should be a common sitting
好，应该有一个共同的坐姿
over there and of course we need to save
在那边，当然我们需要保存
that change to the database I'm going to
对数据库的更改
say I'm going to say the advocate a
说我要说倡导者
repository is typically mapped at the
存储库通常映射到
aggregate so this order is me is not the
聚合，所以这个命令是我不是
aggregate that customer is the aggregate
那个顾客就是总数
all right and all of this will occur in
好吧，所有这一切都会在
a transaction so of course we're I to
一笔交易，所以我们当然是我
throw an exception here with that poem
那首诗在这里丢个例外
then even though I've done all this work
即使我已经完成了所有这些工作
by that point it would all be rollback
到那时，一切都会回滚
you wouldn't see it reflected in these
你不会看到它反映在这些
in the database all right now let's go
现在在数据库中，让我们开始吧
ahead and run this
继续并运行这个
okay looks like it worked very good so
好吧，看起来效果很好，所以
we know that's working now let's query
我们知道它正在工作，让我们查询
the data let's actually interrogate the
数据让我们实际询问
data some more and see what we get and
数据更多，看看我们得到了什么
how we can query it so I looked at I
我们如何查询它，所以我看着我
wrote a manual career using the entity
使用实体撰写了手工职业
manager you said you know the and select
经理你说你知道，然后选择
C from customer see whatever and the IDE
客户从C看什么和IDE
is trying its level headed best to help
正在尽最大努力为您提供帮助
me here but you know I'm a big believer
我在这里，但你知道我是一个大信徒
of not having strings in your code if
如果代码中没有字符串
you can avoid it so I'm gonna use the
你可以避免它，所以我要用
repository to create a custom finder
存储库以创建自定义查找器
methods here so the first Finder is
方法，因此第一个Finder是
gonna be based on the parameter
将基于参数
surprising the predicate something to
令人惊讶的谓词
say give me a collection of customers
说给我一些顾客
find by first and last string at string
按字符串的第一个和最后一个字符串查找
l so that'll work that'll give me all
我会工作的，这会给我所有人
the customers by their first name and
客户的名字和
their last name so let's try that so
他们的姓氏，让我们尝试一下
turn notes and here we're going to say
翻笔记，在这里我们要说
customer posture a find by first and
客户首先要找到并
last so Dave sire and never give us a
最后，戴夫（Dave）父亲，千万不要给我们
collection of people that match
匹配的人的集合
Dave's Dave I'm gonna log out Dave here
戴夫的戴夫我要在这里注销戴夫
all right so to string builder that
好的，所以字符串生成器
reflection to the string David very good
反射到字符串大卫非常好
so there we go so that's let's see if
所以我们去那里，让我们看看是否
that query works as we expected it to
该查询按预期运行
and indeed it has there's our there's
确实有我们的
our different records there so you can
我们在那里的不同记录，因此您可以
see I've got three records here for I've
看到我在这里有三张唱片
got three Dame's basically because I've
因为我有三个
run this program multiple times and my
多次运行此程序，我的
sequel has retained the data across
续集保留了整个数据
those different runs so what I'm going
那些不同的跑步，所以我要去
to do is to keep things a little cleaner
要做的就是保持环境清洁
I'm gonna just say and I say that I want
我只是说，我说我想要
to use the customer repository to delete
使用客户存储库删除
everything first just a clean up the
一切首先只是清理
records here a little bit go ahead and
这里的记录有点继续
rerun the code
重新运行代码
all right so there's now just one days
好吧，现在只有一天
on the console right and we have zero
在控制台右侧，我们有零
orders for this particular one try again
此特定订单再次尝试
try your luck
试试你的运气
there we go so this and this run there
我们去那里，然后在这里跑
more than one order in the you know
您知道的一个以上订单
attached to that customer now that's a a
依附于该客户，现在是
very automatic sort of convention based
非常自动的基于约定的排序
query that query that located in the
查询位于
repository here is based on a convention
此处的存储库基于约定
and this is true across all the
这在所有
different spring data projects you can
您可以使用不同的 spring data 项目
give it a you can create finder methods
给它一个你可以创建查找器方法
that go beyond the default support in
超出了默认支持
these common repositories this
这些常见的存储库
repository supports finding saving
存储库支持查找保存
flushing to needing etc deleting back
冲洗到需要等删除
you know whatever is appropriate for the
你知道什么适合
technology at hand and you can create
手边的技术，您可以创造
custom fibers you can also of course of
定制纤维当然也可以
course create your own custom finder
当然创建自己的自定义查找器
methods with custom crew you know queer
与您知道的自定义工作人员的方法很奇怪
names and so on so five full name string
名字等等五个全名字符串
F string hello here I'm gonna use a
F字符串你好，我要在这里使用
custom peer in there say select C from
那里的自定义同伴说从中选择C
customers see where see that first
客户首先看到的地方
equals F and see that last equals L and
等于F并看到最后等于L和
I refer have to work spring that it
我指的是必须工作的 Spring
needs to know the name of the parameter
需要知道参数的名称
so we give it a pram annotation F and L
所以我们给它一个婴儿车注解F和L
and everything set so let's revisit the
一切都设置好了，让我们重新来看一下
same code basically by full name and
完全相同的代码，全名和
start breaking this up a little bit here
开始在这里分解一点
alright then that could again
好吧那又可以
okay so they are the same same results
好吧，所以他们是相同的结果
as you'd expect nothing is particularly
如您所料，没有什么特别
different here so we have the the
在这里不同，所以我们有
ordered a customer and we have the
订购了一个客户，我们有
orders and that's working just fine now
订单，现在一切正常
in this case I've used a custom query
在这种情况下，我使用了自定义查询
you know I want to be able to do more
你知道我想做得更多
interesting things that don't
有趣的事情
necessarily map necessarily to the
必然映射到
aggregate entities at hand here I might
我可能会汇总手头的实体
want to do things that are you know that
想做你知道的事情
involve derived views of the data right
涉及数据权限的派生视图
so this case we can use a native query
因此在这种情况下，我们可以使用本机查询
okay this is a feature that's nice
好的，这是一个很好的功能
in JP is you can actually get access to
在JP中，您实际上可以访问
the full power of sequel it is a little
续集的全部力量有点
cumbersome and I think this is one of
麻烦，我认为这是其中之一
the big drawbacks of using a norm like
使用类似规范的最大缺点
JP is that you are a long way removed
JP是您很长的路要走
from the native sequel but you can still
来自本地续集，但您仍然可以
get there it's just you need to know
到达那里，只是您需要知道
where to look
在哪里看
ok so we're gonna create a report
好的，我们要创建一个报告
basically when I get a new endpoint that
基本上，当我得到一个新的端点时
returns the collection of orders a
返回订单集合
summary about all orders so I'm gonna
关于所有订单的摘要，所以我要
say order summary ok and order for this
说好订单摘要并为此订购
to work of course we need a project a
工作当然我们需要一个项目
type called an order summary so when use
类型称为订单摘要，因此在使用时
something called a projection and the
所谓的投影和
projection is going to be an
投影将是
implementation of an interface that
接口的实现
we're going to give to JP and that
我们要给JP，
projection is going to have the counts
投影将具有计数
and the SKU all right so we want to
和SKU都很好，所以我们想
create a collection that uses that and
创建一个使用该集合并
we need to tell hibernate and JPA that
我们需要告诉休眠和JPA，
this is going to be mapped to a native
这将被映射到本地
query and a native query will be
查询和本机查询将是
resolved by looking for one of the
通过寻找其中之一解决
native queries that we've registered
我们已经注册的本地查询
with JP a with the name order of
JP a的名称顺序为
acquittal order summary so customer
无罪释放订单摘要，以便客户
order summary in order for us to have
订单摘要，以便我们拥有
that query we need to registered here on
该查询我们需要在此处注册
our entity so I'm going to say act names
我们的实体，所以我要说一下行为名称
native queries I can have more than one
本机查询可以有多个
associated with an entity for example at
与实体关联，例如在
named Nina query
名为Nina的查询
not hibernate challenge persistence and
不休眠挑战持久性和
the name of the crew will be customer
机组人员的名字将是客户
dot order summary and the query itself
点顺序摘要和查询本身
will be select skew as skew and how I as
将选择偏斜作为偏斜以及我如何
challenge so again this is important you
再挑战一次，这很重要
need to have the aliasing there so that
需要在那里有别名，以便
they match with the properties that we
它们与我们的属性相匹配
get from this accountants the other
从这个会计师那里得到另一个
properties in our projection they're
在我们的投影中，它们是
from and it's called orders right when
从，它被称为订单，当
you need the orders group by SKU okay so
您需要按SKU确定订单组，这样
there's our native query it's it's not
这是我们的本机查询，不是
it's not easy to get that right I guess
我猜要做到这一点并不容易
that's because it guess okay so we've
那是因为它猜测还可以，所以我们已经
got now our entity we've got a query
现在我们的实体我们有一个查询
let's see if that works it's actually
让我们看看它是否有效
run this query now that's when to see
现在就可以运行此查询
the results there so take one of those
结果在那里，所以采取其中之一
custom repository to order summary dot
自定义存储库以订购摘要点
for each summary we want to visit the
对于每个摘要，我们要访问
data that comes back and to the same
数据返回到同一
thing as before to string builder a
和以前一样将字符串生成器a
reflection to string summary already
已经反映到字符串摘要
good stuff let's get back in this
好东西让我们回到这个
so that should have given us a proxy but
所以应该给我们一个代理，但是
that's not what I want is it we want to
那不是我想要的，是我们想要的
look at the data
看数据
hmm
嗯
well I guess we'll just have to print it
好吧，我想我们只需要打印它
out the old-fashioned way
走出老式的方式
yeah let's just do that okay so let's
是的，让我们这样做就好了，让我们
say summary dot gets Q as summer in dot
说摘要点在夏天以Q表示Q
get count instances all right write that
得到计数实例可以写
code again
再次编码
all right there you go so you can see
好吧，你去那里，所以你可以看到
that there are three instances of the
有三个实例
city of q0 you know three instances of
q0的城市，您知道的三个实例
skew one two instances of skew - one
倾斜一两个实例倾斜-一
instances q3 so that's actually that you
实例q3，所以实际上
know that means that you know you can
知道那意味着你知道你可以
you can understand the breakdown there
你可以在那里了解故障
right we have a how many you know given
是的，我们有多少你知道的
the four possible skews or rather five
四个可能的偏斜，或者说五个
possible skews what what how many
可能歪斜什么多少
instances of each skew exist you know do
您知道每个偏斜的实例都存在
which customers we didn't look at the
我们没有看过哪些客户
customers here we just looked at the
客户在这里，我们只是看着
summary here using the aggregate
这里总结使用汇总
function count okay so you can get
功能计数还可以，所以您可以获得
access to us you can get access to
访问我们，您可以访问
low-level sequel and I think this is one
低级续集，我认为这是一个
of my favorite features in entirety is
我最喜欢的功能是
to be able to use the low-level sequel
能够使用低级续集
engine which is very powerful and have
引擎非常强大并具有
that mapped automatically to these pipes
自动映射到这些管道的
they strongly typed types right this is
他们强类型输入，对，这是
what we want to happen after all stick
我们到底要坚持什么
it get the work of marshaling whatever
它可以封送处理任何工作
comes back from this into a rather from
从这回到一个相当
this into a typesafe representation that
变成类型安全的表示形式
we can eat okay so now we have a custom
我们可以吃得好，所以现在我们有一个习惯
query we looked at different queries we
我们查询了不同的查询
looked at named query so we are now in a
看着命名查询，所以我们现在在
good place to look at slightly more
好看的好地方
slightly more advanced use cases let's
稍微高级一点的用例
suppose I wanted to build a web
假设我想建立一个网站
application
应用
okay so let's build a web application
好的，让我们构建一个Web应用程序
I've got timely you might recall time
我很及时，你可能会想起时间
uses a view templating engine and I have
使用视图模板引擎，我有
spring boots start a web on the
spring boot 在
classpath and so both of these will let
classpath，所以这两个都会让
me build a web application and then we
我构建一个Web应用程序，然后
build a wrist controller that works with
建立与
this data or not matter rest controller
该数据与否无关紧要
just a regular controller actually a
只是一个常规控制器
views that would be called the customer
被称为客户的视图
controller I'm gonna inject the customer
控制器，我要注入客户
repository here and we'll create an
在这里存储，我们将创建一个
endpoint that has an HTML page with a
具有HTML页面和
view of all the data now think about
查看所有数据，现在考虑
what's happening here I've got that data
这里发生了什么我有数据
customers dot you know
客户点你知道
whatever okay it doesn't matter and the
没关系，没关系，
name of the page customers model data
页面名称客户模型数据
turn customers off I've got a view and
关闭客户我有一个看法，
that view is gonna render and in the
该视图将渲染，并在
view and we'll look at the V in a minute
视图，我们将在一分钟内查看V
but in the view I'm gonna have all the
但我认为所有
customer records and each one of those
客户记录以及其中的每一项
customer records as we seen before
我们以前看到的客户记录
also has a collection of orders well and
也有很多订单
JPA this collection of orders is lazy
JPA这个订单集合很懒
what you actually have in the resulting
您在结果中实际拥有的
runtime application is not a concrete to
运行时应用程序对
hatch set but it's a proxied type that
舱口盖，但这是一种代理类型
comes from the bowels of hibernate we
来自冬眠的肠子
don't need to know what it is or how it
不需要知道它是什么或如何
works but suffice it to say this is not
可以，但是可以说这不是
actually all of the subordinate records
实际上所有下属记录
you only get the subordinate records if
您仅在以下情况下获得下属记录
you touch or iterate over those orders
您触摸或遍历这些订单
so if you just hold on to a pointer to a
因此，如果您仅按住指向
customer and don't and don't do anything
客户，不做任何事情
with the orders themselves then no data
与订单本身，然后没有数据
will be loaded from the database as soon
将尽快从数据库中加载
as you start to iterate through those
当您开始遍历那些
records as I do for example whenever I
像我一样记录
use the to string builder and that
使用字符串生成器
recursively you know it recursively and
递归地，你递归地知道它，
reflectively descends into the orders
反思地下降到命令
collection whenever you start to do that
每当您开始收集时
it didn't have to load the data from the
它不必从
database right and in the best case it's
数据库权利，最好的情况是
just one more extra query in the worst
在最坏的情况下仅再进行一次额外查询
case you get the n plus one problem
如果你遇到n加一的问题
where you have a single select for each
您可以为每个选择一个
order and that's a whole other topic we
订单，这是我们的另一个主题
could talk about a thousand different
可以说一千种不同
things related to query optimization and
与查询优化有关的事情以及
so on but for our purposes what we need
等等，但出于我们的目的，我们需要
to know is that this is my default lazy
知道这是我的默认懒惰
and so if you send this customer to
因此，如果您将此客户发送给
another context outside of a current
当前之外的另一个上下文
transaction outside of the current
当前以外的交易
running transaction with JPA
使用JPA进行交易
well then we're gonna run into some
好吧，我们会遇到一些
trouble if we try and visit any of those
麻烦，如果我们尝试访问任何一个
orders and so if you imagine we move
订单，所以如果你想像我们搬家
this customer to a view to be rendered
该客户要呈现的视图
ok and for Narender it we need to be
好，对于Narender，我们需要
able to make sure that that data gets
能够确保获得的数据
loaded correctly so here I am doing
正确加载，所以我在这里
nothing to take care of those records
没有什么可以照顾那些记录
and I still want to render it in this
我仍然想在此渲染它
view and this view I have to create I'll
视图，我必须创建此视图
create the view here
在这里创建视图
horse mane resources templates create a
马鬃毛资源模板创建一个
new file here called customers that eh -
这里的新文件称为eh-
no that's a a view template for time
不，那是时间的视图模板
leaf and I am nothing if not lazy my
叶，如果不偷懒，我什么都不是
friend so I'm gonna just copy it here
朋友，所以我要在这里复制
okay
好的
paste and you can see what's happening
粘贴，您可以看到发生了什么
here at it's a very simple view it says
这是一个非常简单的视图
for each customers see and the customers
为每个客户见和客户
model attribute print out an h2 element
模型属性打印出h2元素
with the first name in the last name and
姓氏中的名字和
then visit each order and print out the
然后访问每个订单并打印出
ID and the SKU alright and I suppose we
ID和SKU好吧，我想我们
could actually a.m.
实际上可能是
have some sort of delimiter here I guess
我猜这里有某种分隔符
let's think about that how would that
让我们考虑一下
work style order I can top:1px sell them
我可以的工作风格订单：1px卖给他们
back
背部
David go so now you can see hopefully if
大卫走了，现在你可以希望看到
I HTML by CSS foo is not so terrible you
我用CSS foo编写的HTML并不那么糟糕
can see which order you know you can see
可以看到您知道可以看到的订单
all the different ores actually each
实际上所有不同的矿石
line will be in order side we don't need
线将在我们不需要的一侧
that at all so let's just leave that is
那就让我们离开吧
as is and then see what happens if we
照原样，然后看看如果我们
run this code so this is a spring MVC
运行此代码，所以这是一个Spring MVC
controller localhost:8080
控制器本地主机：8080
customers dot view and there we go we
客户点视图，然后我们去
can see the ID of this cube and the XS Q
可以看到此多维数据集的ID和XS Q
itself and we can see how many customers
本身，我们可以看到有多少客户
we have in the database so again this is
我们在数据库中，所以这又是
a random random list of orders just to
随机的随机订单清单
demonstrate the point but um you can see
证明这一点，但嗯，你可以看到
SKU zero isn't there one two three times
SKU零不存在1 2 3倍
all right so if we go back to our report
好的，所以如果我们返回报告
here you can see that it says Q zero has
在这里您可以看到它说Q 0有
three instances so that's working out
三个实例，所以正在解决
just fine right we're actually able to
很好，我们实际上能够
look at the data even though we've moved
看看数据，即使我们已经移动
it across a different boundary outside
它跨越外面的另一个边界
of the transaction the way we're able to
交易方式
do that is that by default spring boots
这样做是默认情况下的 spring boot
configures the open session and you open
配置打开的会话，然后您打开
entity manager and view pattern so here
实体经理和视图模式，所以在这里
it's a spring day open API open and view
这是一个开放的 Spring 开放API，可以查看
equals true if I set it to false what
如果我将其设置为false，则等于true
you might want to do you know you might
你可能想做，你知道你可能
want to be defensive about what you pass
想要对自己通过的内容保持防御
down to the view layer so that by that
向下到视图层，这样
point you can't
点你不能
they hit the database so if I hit that
他们打了数据库，所以如果我打那个
if I specify that property and set it to
如果我指定该属性并将其设置为
be false let's see what happens if I now
是假的，让我们看看如果我现在会发生什么
visit that page go right the big error
访问该页面去大错误
that we just we were just given is that
我们刚刚得到的是
it's able to lazily initialize a
它可以延迟初始化
collection of role blah blah blah so
角色的集合等等等等等等
it's it's telling me that there's no
就是告诉我没有
session opens for it to then materialize
会议开始，然后实现
that lazy collection of data so you
懒惰的数据收集，所以你
don't you know you should know about
你不知道你应该知道
this feature it's being configured for
此功能正在配置中
you automatically
你自动
we've automatically spring his ad for
我们会自动为其投放广告
the longest time the open entity manager
公开时间最长的实体经理
a new filter that's this thing here and
一个新的过滤器就是这个东西，
spring boot I'm not gonna just
spring boot ，我不会只是
configured for you if you wanted there
如果您想在那里为您配置
so this has been around forever it's
所以这已经永远存在了
just nice to know that spring food has
很高兴知道 Spring 食品有
gone the extra mile to make that
付出了更多的努力
available and to make it work for you
可用并使其适合您
automatically so that things just work
自动运行，以便一切正常
okay all right so now we've got an
好吧，所以现在我们有一个
application it has a endpoint an HTML
应用程序，它具有终结点HTML
application HTML view but this is data
应用程序HTML视图，但这是数据
this is order data and so you might say
这是订单数据，所以您可能会说
that this is especially in the world of
尤其是在
you know being in compromised by hackers
你知道被黑客入侵
and and we're the finance and all that
而且我们是财务人员
kinda stuff this kind of stuff is super
有点东西这种东西超级好
important it's important that we have
重要的是我们拥有
the ability to look at the data to be
查看数据的能力
able to see what's happening to it and
能够看到发生了什么事，
so for this reason we're gonna use
因此，出于这个原因，我们将使用
spring datas support for auditing okay
spring数据支持审计还可以
we're gonna actually externalize we're
我们实际上将外部化
going to configure some of the sums of
将配置一些总和
information that we want to be visible
我们希望可见的信息
in every single record including the
在每条记录中，包括
data was created they date it was
数据创建于日期
modified and possibly even the user who
修改，甚至可能是用户
created and/or modified that that entity
创建和/或修改该实体
so we want to have that visible in order
所以我们希望顺序可见
for us to do that we need to say first
为了做到这一点，我们需要先说
of all we have to go through and say at
我们必须经历的所有事情
naval JP are they
海军JP是
and JPA oddity and then for each entity
和JPA奇数，然后对每个实体
we need to actually configure a number
我们需要实际配置一个数字
of redundant things things that you
多余的东西，你的东西
would think we could centralize and
会认为我们可以集中精力，
actually that's what we're going to do
实际上这就是我们要做的
is we're gonna centralize all these
是我们要集中所有这些吗
things that are repeated across the
在整个过程中重复的事情
different entities so let's go back down
不同的实体，让我们回头看看
to our entities here the order and the
给我们的实体在这里的顺序和
customers and create a map superclass
客户并创建地图超类
this is a JP isn't it allows you to
这是JP是不是可以让您
define things that should be common
定义应该通用的东西
across given entities in a single place
跨给定实体的单个位置
and the new takes just extend them so
而新的需要只是扩展他们，所以
class let's just call this map auditable
类，让我们将此地图称为可审核
base if that's a word and I'm gonna say
如果这是一个词的基础，我要说
that we want to apply a
我们想要应用
jp8 entity listener okay so this is a
jp8实体侦听器好了，所以这是一个
listener called the auditing and to do
监听器叫审计并做
this run this is from spring data GPA
这是来自 spring data GPA
again we provide the support out of the
再次，我们提供了支持
box you just call back in JPA and when
框，您只需在JPA中回电
define our ID in a single place you know
在您知道的一个地方定义我们的ID
that all records will have a so we're
所有记录都会有一个
good are tormenting primary key we want
善于折磨我们想要的主键
to have a an idea of when the when this
了解何时该何时
record was created I'm gonna create any
记录已创建，我要创建任何
local date/time field you could also use
您还可以使用本地日期/时间字段
a m8w till date although I wouldn't it's
m8w直到日期，尽管我不是
Java it's 2018 so use the right thing
Java到了2018年，请正确使用
here and we're gonna use the one the
在这里，我们将使用一个
last modified date so again local save
最后修改日期，因此再次本地保存
time modified and we want things created
时间修改了，我们希望创造事物
by that's the user and we'll come back
就是那个用户，我们会回来的
to this in a second but it's done it's a
一秒钟就完成了，但这是一个
string yet it could be a good it could
字符串，但它可能是一个好习惯
be a complete object that you map to a
成为您映射到的完整对象
tape going to an entity in your
磁带将进入您的实体
because you would want but in this case
因为你想要但在这种情况下
it's gonna be just a string the name of
它只是名称的字符串
the Creator user and modified by okay so
创建者用户并通过修改进行了修改
I'm gonna be modifier right so these
我会成为修正者，所以这些
things have to be provided by this
事情必须由这个提供
auditing entity listener and this is
审核实体侦听器，这是
something that spring data will do for
Spring 的数据将为
you it looks for those annotations it
你寻找那些注释
doesn't matter what you name yeah fields
不管你叫什么名字
and alternate all that thing is doing
并交替做所有事情
it's taking advantage of hooks that you
利用钩子，你
have and you can also use a joint for
有，你也可以使用关节
example pre remove pre persist pretty
示例pre remove pre持久漂亮
update pretty destroy post remove all
更新漂亮销毁帖子删除所有
these lifecycle hooks so if you create a
这些生命周期挂钩，所以如果您创建一个
method here for avoid post remove get a
避免后删除的方法
logger here I get two pictures to do
记录器在这里，我有两张照片要做
this okay whatever you could log
好的，无论您可以登录
something in there what everyone do any
每个人都在做什么
kind of validation so those those things
这样的验证，那些东西
are there for you but I'm gonna just
有你在那儿，但我会
leave that here and now we're going to
离开这里，现在我们要
extend our order and our customer from
扩展我们的订单和我们的客户
that site so let's do that
该网站，所以让我们这样做
where's our types here oh yeah down here
我们的类型在哪里哦，是的，在这里
extends mapped auditable face and
扩展了映射的可审核面并
extends mapped
扩展映射
ah difficulties and in this case we
啊困难，在这种情况下，我们
don't need the ids anymore that'll break
不再需要ID了
our Lombok configuration but the idea by
我们的龙目岛配置，但想法
the base class so I'm happy for that
基础课，所以我为此感到高兴
let's see ya bye and good bye okay so
让我们看看你再见，再见，好吧
now let's run the code again okay do we
现在让我们再次运行代码，好吧
see the data here
在这里查看数据
now it says created and modified so
现在它说创建和修改，所以
again that's the date and time of the
再次，这是日期和时间
creation of these instances now the
现在创建这些实例
creator field and the modifier field
创建者字段和修饰符字段
then the user name or the thing that we
然后是用户名或我们
can use to trace who made this change
可以用来追踪是谁做了这个改变
are at the moment absent in order for us
为了我们现在缺席
to do that in order for us to have that
这样做是为了让我们拥有
information wait to tell Spinetta
信息等待告诉斯皮内塔
where to look for that information right
在哪里可以找到该信息
it's any kind of any regular old spring
这是任何常规的旧 Spring
be I'm gonna call it auditor and it has
我要称它为审计师
to implement auditor aware and it has to
实施审核员意识，并且必须
produce the information that's looking
产生正在寻找的信息
for so they can get Kurt auditor and -
为此，他们可以聘请Kurt审核员，并且-
you know it does nobody then it's empty
你知道它没有人，那么它是空的
it's something in it well of course this
这当然很好
could be we could use spring security
可能是我们可以使用Spring Security
right if I if I had spring security on
对，如果我有Spring Security 保障
the con on the classpath I could take
我可以接受的classpath的缺点
the security context dot get you know
安全上下文点让您知道
current context and blah blah and get
当前上下文等等等等，得到
principal and then stash that there I
校长然后藏在那里
could return an optional of Java secure
可以返回可选的Java安全
your principal wherever you whatever you
校长无论你在哪里
want to do right whatever whatever your
想要做正确的事
mechanism for tracing users is but in
跟踪用户的机制是
our case I'm just gonna I'm gonna inject
我们的情况下，我要注射
the username my local UNIX username so
用户名我的本地UNIX用户名
user and I'll inject that into the
用户，然后将其注入
constructor there's a very simple
构造函数有一个非常简单的
example very silly but simple as that
这个例子很愚蠢，但是很简单
obviously in a production application
显然在生产应用中
this would make very little sense since
这将毫无意义，因为
most code doesn't run yeah most of this
大多数代码都无法运行是的
most of the time you'll have our friend
大多数时候，您会拥有我们的朋友
of front-end website so you want to want
前端网站，因此您想要
to know who the authenticated user is
知道谁是经过身份验证的用户
not the
不是
they process how much the stuff or the
他们处理多少东西或
name of the user on the operating system
操作系统上的用户名
one which under which this application
一个根据这个应用程序
is running so optional of this user
正在运行，因此该用户是可选的
alright so there we are so there's my my
好吧，所以我们在那里，还有我的我
hard-coded using and password thing this
硬编码使用和密码的东西
callback is what's important so just
回调是重要的，所以
implement that callback and tell it
实现该回调并告诉它
where to find the data and let's see
在哪里找到数据，让我们看看
what that gets us
是什么让我们
already but they go at this jail all day
已经，但是他们整天都在这个监狱里
long so it's now filling in those fields
很长，所以现在正在填充这些领域
for us just as we'd hoped
就像我们希望的那样
okay now this is I think this is good
好吧，这是我认为这很好
this is a good first step in auditing
这是审核的良好第一步
the data that's it
就是这样的数据
that's it you know high-stakes
那就是你知道的高风险
environment where you need to have a
您需要有一个环境
full audit trail on every single change
每次更改的完整审核记录
every single mutation to every single
每一个单突变
entity everywhere in the system if
实体在系统中到处都是
you're in that situation then this may
你在那种情况下，这可能
not be enough you might want to see
你可能想看看还不够
every single change every single record
每一个变化每一个记录
and they both to go to go back in time
他们俩都去时光倒流
and see that and so there's a lot of
看到了，所以有很多
different other use cases for this as
与此不同的其他用例
well change data capture for dental is
牙科的好变化数据捕获是
another use case where you endo to see
您可以看到的另一个用例
the changes to a given entity and then
对给定实体的更改，然后
then we pay them later on for example I
那我们以后再付钱给我
mean there's a lot of reasons why you
意思是说你有很多原因
might want this and you should have it
可能想要这个，你应该拥有它
there's a is it we have to have any
有一个是我们必须有任何
community and relational databases are
社区和关系数据库是
good at this kind of thing so we are
擅长这种事情，所以我们
gonna use a project called hibernate on
将使用一个名为休眠的项目
bears which is it spelled env ers I'm
熊，那是我拼写的吗
not sure where that comes from in French
不确定从法国来的
on there needs to like it's a
那里需要喜欢它
preposition to it you know I think I'm
介词，你知道我想我是
not sure what the here but I'm gonna use
不知道这里是什么，但我要用
that okay I'm even thinking of that
好吧，我什至在想那个
actually I'm not even sure we don't bail
其实我什至不知道我们不保释
me so whatever we have this preposition
我，所以不管我们有这个介词
we have this word I'm bear I'm bears and
我们有这个词，我是熊，我是熊，
that when I go ahead and bring that into
当我继续并将其带入
the project here and we have a module
这里的项目，我们有一个模块
that a spring that a module that works
那个Spring ，一个有效的模块
with our bears okay
与我们的熊好
we're looking for my data and I don't
我们正在寻找我的数据，但我没有
think a lot of people know about this
想很多人都知道
part which is a shame because it's
可耻的部分，因为
really really useful so all we need to
真的非常有用，所以我们需要
do is we need to tell first of all we
首先，我们需要告诉我们
need to tell spring and spring that a JP
需要告诉 Spring 和 Spring ，JP
particular where to find the you know
特别是在哪里找到你知道的
where how to configure our repositories
在哪里配置我们的仓库
with our bears
与我们的熊
in the mix right so we have trap to
在混合中，所以我们有陷阱
override the default that ojp a
覆盖ojp a的默认值
repository support in the springboard
跳板中的存储库支持
auto-configuration
自动配置
we override it by using the armrest
我们通过使用扶手来覆盖它
revision repository factory beam and
修订版本库工厂梁和
then we have to make our entities
然后我们必须使我们的实体
auditable so let's go down here to each
可审核的，所以让我们深入了解每个
entity there it is audited where's our
那里的实体，我们的审计在哪里
order and find it today all right now
立即订购并立即找到它
this is from the hibernate project
这是来自休眠项目
hibernate on bears and it's a really
在熊上冬眠，这真的
useful project and it will work with
有用的项目，它将与
hibernate and we've already got
冬眠，我们已经有
hibernate running so we don't have to do
休眠运行，因此我们不必做
much to get that to work beyond what we
使它超出我们的工作范围还有很多
have there
有那里
so let's go ahead and just run this and
因此，让我们继续运行，然后运行
take a look at the resulting schema and
看一下结果架构
we should actually interrogate the
我们实际上应该审问
repository to do that in a second but
储存库可以在一秒钟内完成
let's just see if it's stuff like
让我们看看它是否像
everything should be fine okay so you
一切都会好起来的，所以你
can see that it's done it's done
可以看到已经完成了
everything as before but it's also
一切都像以前一样，但是
clearly these tables called customers
这些表显然称为客户
AUD customers but of customers AUD and
澳元客户，但客户的澳元和
ordered ad and it's great the schema for
有序广告，它的架构很棒
all that - all right so select all from
所有-好的，所以从中选择所有
this buh-buh-bah create table orders of
这个buh-buh-bah创建以下表格的订单
AUD there's another table like read info
AUD还有另一张桌子，如已读信息
and we can see that all show tables
我们可以看到所有显示表
there we are and so I expect your backed
我们在那里，所以我希望您的支持
off from orders there's our 11 rows like
从订单关闭有我们的11行
offerings quarters
提供的季度
so we're gonna see it's an interesting
所以我们会发现这很有趣
formation there but we don't have to
在那里形成，但我们不必
worry about it we don't have to we don't
不用担心，我们不必
have to drill down and find reverse
必须向下钻取并找到反向
engineer that schema although you
尽管您可以设计该架构
definitely show it at some point what we
肯定在某个时候展示它
want to do is just use the repository to
要做的只是使用存储库
interact for that data and so that's
为该数据进行交互，因此
fairly straightforward we're just gonna
相当简单，我们只是
go to our repository and extend also
转到我们的存储库并扩展
another interface a revision repository
另一个接口，修订版本库
and that's going to manage entity the
这将管理实体
type of customer primary keys except
客户主键的类型，除了
long and the type of the revision will
时间长短和修订类型
be mapped by an integer and with that
用一个整数映射
basic extension in place we can now add
基本扩展到位，我们现在可以添加
one more printout so we we've got we got
再打印一份，所以我们得到了
to make some changes here we've got
在这里进行一些更改
let's see we've got Dave but we've only
让我们看看我们有戴夫，但我们只有
we've only changed Dave twice we changed
我们只改变了戴夫两次
everything else once right we created
我们创建的所有其他内容
the record we created we actually
我们创建的记录实际上
modified everything twice so far let's
到目前为止，我们已经两次修改了所有内容
go ahead and now modify Dave just in
继续，现在修改Dave
particular to illustrate the point so
特别是要说明这一点
I'm gonna find Dave desire to visit Dave
我会发现戴夫渴望访问戴夫
is it each record in the collection that
是集合中的每条记录吗？
comes back and we're gonna change Dave
回来，我们要换戴夫
to David I'm not sure that's is I don't
大卫，我不确定那是不是
know if he appreciates being called
知道他是否喜欢被叫
David but it will just do it because
大卫，但它只会这样做，因为
it's a when is a short name for the
这是when的简称
other and we're gonna say customer and
其他，我们要说客户和
pops are unsaved Dave and now another
流行音乐是未保存的戴夫，现在又是另一个
transaction I'm gonna get back to each
我要回去的交易
record all right this is of course I'm
记录好吧，这当然是我
talking about the good the doctor gave
谈论医生给的好处
it sire
父亲
is a friend and a hero so here we go
是朋友和英雄，所以我们开始
we've got the we've got David I'm gonna
我们要有大卫，我要
get the ID so oh I forgot the map
得到ID，所以我忘了地图
superclass also should have the at that
超类也应该在那个
annotation from Lombok to get the
从龙目岛注解以获取
getters and setters which makes this
吸气剂和二传手这使得
easier very good and now I'm going to
更容易非常好，现在我要
visit the repository I'm going to say
访问我要说的存储库
find revision for ID and that's it and
找到ID的修订，仅此而已
then find my provisions for the customer
然后找到我为客户准备的
entity whose ID is equal to yes so we
实体的ID等于yes，因此我们
can actually simplify that a little bit
实际上可以简化一点
here and then put each revision that
在这里，然后把每个修订
comes back that what we get so log that
回来，我们得到了什么，所以记录
info vision maybe I get metadata go
信息视觉也许我得到了元数据
there with a string vision
在那里有远见
all right so all I'm doing is I'm
好吧，所以我要做的就是
putting out the revision metadata for a
推出版本的修订元数据
given entity and we'll see it logged
给定的实体，我们将看到它已记录
there I'm looking up Dave just a just a
在那里我正在寻找戴夫只是一个
DB scale okay let's just put it see what
数据库规模好吧，让我们看看
we get
我们得到
cool so there we are we've got three
很酷，所以我们有三个
records three provisions here you can
在这里可以记录三个规定
see we've got ID five and here's the
看到我们有ID 5，这是
different dates right 8:26 well these
不同的日期吧8:26这些
are all basically the same time I want
基本上都在同一时间
to click it actually yeah let's um
点击它实际上是的，让我们
introduce a pause alright this entry to
给这个条目引入一个暂停
pause here
在这里暂停
two seconds sleep there we are okay
两秒钟睡在那里，我们还好
there we go so we can see that the
我们去那里，所以我们可以看到
second change happened at thirty three
第二次改变发生在33
seconds after and third change captain
第三次换队后
at thirty five seconds after so we can
在三十五秒后，我们可以
see the data there and also you can see
看到那里的数据，你也可以看到
the changes look at that you can see
这些变化让您看到
here's the first instance of that record
这是该记录的第一个实例
called Dave and there were zero orders
叫戴夫，零订单
here's the second to that record called
这是该记录的第二个
Dave and here are all the orders here's
戴夫，这是所有的订单
the third instance of that record for
该记录的第三个实例
David not Dave the same number order so
大卫没有戴夫相同的数字顺序
he can see the associated entity and the
他可以看到关联的实体和
time when those changes happened so I
这些变化发生的时间，所以我
think if you need that kind of thing
想想你是否需要那种东西
it's very very powerful now I did it I
现在我做到了，它非常非常强大
just slapped at audited on all the
只是对所有
entities in my application naturally you
实体在我的应用程序中自然是你
may not want that for everybody in here
可能不希望每个人都这样
all good crap and you don't need to
所有的废话，你不需要
write you can use at audited on the
您可以在审核时使用的文字
entity that you care about the ones that
您关心的实体
you want to be audited and you can also
您想接受审核，也可以
then exclude other entities from that
然后从中排除其他实体
for example but if you do have an entity
例如，但如果您有实体
that references another one for example
例如引用另一个
in this case the customer reference is
在这种情况下，客户参考是
over the orders then they both need
超过订单，那么他们俩都需要
audited or you need to exclude it right
已审核，或者您需要排除它
tonight so if you do that it's out of
今晚，所以如果你这样做的话
the field here then it'll exclude that
此处的字段将排除
from the auditing it won't change it
从审计它不会改变它
won't capture the revisions to that
不会捕获该版本的修订
subordinate collection they're referred
被推荐的下属集合
it captured in this case alright so
它在这种情况下被捕获了，所以
we've looked at GPA GPA of course is a
我们看过GPA GPA当然是
trustworthy technology that's been
值得信赖的技术
around for a long time I think that for
我想了很久
a lot of people JPA is gonna be you know
很多人JPA会成为你知道的
it's gonna be a very convenient fit
这将是一个非常方便的选择
it lets you work with objects and if
它使您可以处理对象，如果
you're just trying to get a few objects
你只是想拿一些东西
in your domain model persisted into a
在您的域模型中持续存在
database and you don't mind giving up
数据库，你不介意放弃
some control over the queries then you
对查询进行一些控制，然后您
should you should take a look at the APA
您应该看看APA吗
there's some really good advice out
有一些非常好的建议
there on on how to improve JP
关于如何提高JP
performance for example so hyper systems
性能，例如超级系统
giving a shout out here to my
在这里向我大喊
my friend Vlad's amazing book so if you
我朋友弗拉德（Vlad）的精彩著作
get a chance maybe read this this book
有机会读这本书
you can buy it here too high persistence
你可以在这里买它持久性太高
that I owe it's run it's written by glad
我欠它的运行它是由高兴写的
me how see ya I'm not even I I don't
我怎么看呀，我什至没有我不
want to butcher his name but he's a
想屠杀他的名字，但他是一个
developer advocate he's a developer
开发者拥护者，他是开发者
advocate for the hibernate team and you
冬眠团队的拥护者和你
know he he's got some very good examples
知道他有一些很好的例子
on how to make hibernate absolutely
关于如何使自己完全冬眠
scream in terms of speed you know so I
你知道的速度尖叫，所以我
definitely recommend that I think the
绝对建议我认为
most powerful part of your already BMS
BMS中最强大的部分
is sequel right so I don't want to give
是续集对，所以我不想放弃
up sequel I don't want to have control I
续集我不想控制我
want to lose that control and so you
想失去控制权，所以你
should be aware of these little
应该注意这些小事
opportunities to regain that control
重新获得控制权的机会
it's nice to have your objects mapped
映射对象很好
nicely to a to the different structures
很好地适应了不同的结构
in your database but that shouldn't mean
在您的数据库中，但这并不意味着
that you lose control and so it's very
你失去控制，所以这是非常
important to keep keep in mind what's
重要的是要记住什么
happening behind the scenes that's why
发生在幕后的原因
one of the first things I did was to
我做的第一件事就是
illustrate all the different sequel
说明所有不同的续集
statements at RA that are executing here
RA此处执行的语句
when we run this code now keep in mind
现在，当我们运行此代码时，请记住
it's not actually that in performant to
实际上并不是表演
run a lot of sequel statements
运行很多续集声明
especially if you're doing it in a batch
特别是如果您要分批处理
inside of a transaction it's in
在交易内部
performance equate if each one of these
性能等同于这些条件中的每一项
sequel queries was a separate
续集查询是单独的
transaction that would be very very slow
交易将非常非常缓慢
but to run in three or four sequel
但要连续三到四个续集
statements in a single transaction that
单笔交易中的陈述
it's it's painless you know we have
你知道我们有没有痛苦
looked at the absolute basics of JPA I
看了JPA I的绝对基础
didn't look at any any particular
没什么特别的
specific features of our implementation
我们实施的具体特点
we didn't spend a lot of time looking at
我们没有花很多时间在看
mapping there's a you know there's
映射有一个你知道有
billions of pages I'm sure on how to map
我确定如何绘制数十亿个页面
entities to other types of entities I
实体到其他类型的实体我
did a slightly more interesting example
做了一个更有趣的例子
here with a map superclass and a
这里有一个地图超类和一个
one-to-many relationship but there's a
一对多关系，但是有一个
whole number of other things you can do
您可以做的其他事情的总数
here obviously I hope you will pursue
显然在这里我希望你会追求
that at your leisure and we looked at
在您闲暇时，我们看着
some of the things that could be
一些可能是
considered anti-patterns like this open
被认为像这样的反模式开放
entity manager and view thing some
实体经理并查看事物
people really don't like that and
人们真的不喜欢
actually spring boot I think it will log
实际上我认为它会启动
it out won't it let's see
出来吧，让我们看看
schooling well I think it's not foreign
学得好我认为这不是外国的
is it yeah it actually does look at that
是的，它实际上确实在看那个
so spring JPA open and view is enabled
所以 Spring JPA打开并启用了视图
by default therefore database queries
因此默认情况下数据库查询
maybe four maybe perform during view
也许四个可能在观看期间执行
rendering explicitly configure about a
渲染显式配置
lot to disable this morning so again if
今天早上有很多禁用功能，所以再次
you don't want that um you know it's
你不想要那个嗯，你知道那是
nice to know about it so has to have it
很高兴知道它，所以必须拥有它
if you need it and then if you're just
如果您需要它，然后如果您只是
trying to get enough an application up
尝试获取足够的应用程序
and running as quick as possible as we
并尽可能快地运行
did here then that's the that's the tool
在这里做了那就是那个工具
for you what advice you might wanna get
给你什么你可能想要得到的建议
rid of it and you know your mileage may
摆脱它，你知道你的里程可能
vary when you start moving these wires
开始移动这些导线时会有所不同
over rest api and so on so you have to
其余的api等，因此您必须
have to care about that you have to care
不得不在乎你必须在乎
about what happens there with that my
关于那件事
friends I thank you for watching and I
朋友，我感谢你的收看，我
hope you got something out of this and
希望你从中得到一些东西
we'll see you next time
下次见
you
您